{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Carpet Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40040/":{"taskOID":40040,"originalTaskOID":40040,"setID":364,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6973,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damaged carpet you need repaired? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10314,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Discolored or stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10356,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burned or melted","answerDisplayText":"Burned or melted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10357,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","answerDisplayText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10358,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seam","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10359,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn or fraying","answerDisplayText":"Worn or fraying","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10360,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs re-stretching","answerDisplayText":"Needs re-stretching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10361,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","answerDisplayText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4042,"questionDisplayText":"Extra Carpet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have any extra carpet saved from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6973,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Problem","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damaged carpet you need repaired? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10314,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Discolored or stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10356,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burned or melted","answerDisplayText":"Burned or melted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10357,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","answerDisplayText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10358,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seam","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10359,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn or fraying","answerDisplayText":"Worn or fraying","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10360,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs re-stretching","answerDisplayText":"Needs re-stretching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10361,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","answerDisplayText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10314,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Discolored or stained","answerDisplayText":"Discolored or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10356,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Burned or melted","answerDisplayText":"Burned or melted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10357,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","answerDisplayText":"Loose or detached from tack strip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10358,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Exposed seam","answerDisplayText":"Exposed seam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10359,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Worn or fraying","answerDisplayText":"Worn or fraying","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10360,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Needs re-stretching","answerDisplayText":"Needs re-stretching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10361,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","answerDisplayText":"Attach to newly installed flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4042,"questionDisplayText":"Extra Carpet","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you have any extra carpet saved from installation?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/40040/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40040,"taskName":"Carpet - Repair, Refasten, or Stretch","taskDescription":"Repair, Refasten, or Stretch Carpeting","xmTaskDescriptor":"Carpet Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":35,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpet seam floor fasten Stretch","textMessagingName":"Repair Carpet","rolloverLongDesc":"Can remove wrinkles, sometimes replace warn or stained areas \u0026 reattach loose carpeting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Correct problems with existing carpeting.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair, Refasten, or Stretch Carpeting.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Carpet Repair \u0026 Carpet Stretching","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":11,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Carpet Repair, Refasten or Stretch","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Carpet - Repair, Refasten, or Stretch","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Carpet Repair Project","urlName":"Carpet-Repair-Refasten-or-Stretch","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Carpet Repair \u0026 Stretching Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Carpet,seam,floor,fasten,Stretch,berber","emcCategoryOid":-12032,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":364,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}